let's go bees 33 miles away show me that
[Music]
yeah we did stop by flying today George
got Co oh yeah so we were over piling to
the urban sprawl of Colorado we got ways
up here navigating us for fix toboggan
ways last night big victory yeah it's
really smooth
yeah right anyone out there got any on
run we sold the neon last night yeah I
get there first person to get the Rio to
be honest yeah make it but Basil's got
USPS to deliver Amazon so that's the
real religion of America right
but people got yawns today vanilla girl
is telling us that really somethin Ella
girl USPS really hasn't been on the
slack I don't know what's up service
yeah they have literally Oh baby that
I'm good yeah Wyoming is actually really
nice there's just no t-mobile yeah yeah
there's no service
virtually Chris got his nice taking us
through the urban sprawl of Colorado
yeah Colorado's nicely generate you see
see where we're engaged if you're caught
up in a nice engaged up here Emily
what's the MOA said you're gonna stop at
that moment
there's bowling Wes do you have to go to
see the tour Oh Mall of America oh boy
Colorado we got a turn turn right and
I'll be nice and now you linked to my
sensor over there you know that that car
is gonna pass and now we got nobody
night you should automatically slow up a
little Jeff nice if you can do that okay
say is it clear to do
yawns happy staying cool
of course you know in this car if we get
below 20 miles an hour it turns off its
gonna turn off yeah Common Council to be
too rough
oh sorry what a big poofy
a bumpy oh yeah for paracin this Marcel
since it's a nice loft
this
just open finally give us better MSG
we're getting 32.8 right now in DG bomb
which is pretty insane given that this
car is rated for like 429 I mean any
cruise control will improve your
efficiency yeah
not specifically open palette you know
style of staying like far back from the
car in front of it will also improve
your efficiency because the less you
accelerate and decelerate the more no
it's car than the CVT but literally like
if you're trying to get from point A to
point B the less yeah like if you just
take the absolute value of acceleration
and take the mean of that the lower that
is the more efficient actually going
lower speeds is generally better too oh
[Music]
that's the same bug we've he's saying
the stock cruise on his rav4 has the
same false positive issues Oh
we're obviously using the same radar on
BC the nice thing about open pilot
versus the stock system is when the
stock system messes up nobody knows
right you just like now we know a little
but oh so we get all this back and we
can analyze that data so what's
happening is on the radar has this flag
for whether a point is measured or
computed and something the computed ones
will drift over into your lane even when
the real object does not but you need to
rely on the computed ones in the rain
on the truck as being in front of you on
a corner
yeah well corners a whole different
problem how it's just a lot better at
that because we have a model that
predicts where you'll go and does just
use your car y'all right
I'll be yes you guys are hopefully gonna
get to see a speed like a resume driving
man you'll be speed to low kind of thing
right here yeah we're just gonna get a
comma cancel speed you low again yeah
see that's cool
yes please once I'm above 20 I can hit
the button resume the cruise controls
talk to do that
well pods pretty good at urban sprawl
ready to drive the flat roads of Kansas
that we are
see what its gonna do here this looks
like that guy's going down that guy's
going there someone she confused Oh
golly good job good
we should show it so we're gonna change
it to show your scent speed when you're
in the ways you like this
so could you make it steer it steers
yeah Toyota will steer all that have a
zero as well but it's just going Prius
will go to zero there's miss Bunter
assume we fix all facts yes
turn it on Mulberry Street hurry there's
a real baby
oh man berries blueberries raspberries
[Music]
car with auto parking but no LK can
autopilot be ported yeah Paulo we were
looking at 50s this morning around not
so much Colorado now Ralph boys are kind
of common again poor whenever you have
suburbs around yeah well I miss you Basu
bees which switching I need fun for open
pilot Toyota rav4 drive but which
switches all depends what you want to do
with your giraffe yeah Oh slash
another's get that io / Drive I think
yeah yeah that will show you what
configuration you want for your giraffe
depending on what you want to do yes
we're still undecided on how far east
will go
my f-150 has electronic steer assist
yeah we were watching some video park
assist with our f-150 2011 f-150 has
alright let's see if we're gonna get a
fusion with this UPS truck probably not
it's probably unrealistic
maybe there's a maybe that's a neon on
that
why was that if the car so it will pick
it up eventually the problem is it has
to do a fusion with vision if a car is
fully stopped cross got bigger you have
across the size weight changes babies do
you do that because you're a sturdier
gets bigger cross more sugar that's
smaller than it's like too small now I
agree that's a change which card is open
Patrick best I'm pretty happy with like
right here the torque from the toy is
helping us out specific this car is
struggling a little on the highway but
the urban sprawl the rare force is
killing her
good day Colorado's a lot of movements
problem that's right
Yeah right how crazy is that that that
thing is going ways and driving your car
and yeah
sounds French should you make everything
disappear
is Priya's Prius aimed to open it as
normal
the Prius taxes the case tonight because
the same as in oak trees Brian I would
love to see any stock says to drive it
as urban sprawl right now one of those
hearings on that
oh there could be I mean I wonder
villain why does he have his left
blinker on just going behind dr Brazos
right after we park the car don't do
that
she'd be quiet the exact time I like
that I was feeling that been turning bad
snow basically if you wouldn't use
cruise control you shouldn't use this
last night we sell our traction quite a
bit like there were signs I should say
to turn off your Christmas yeah I never
think you are to be fair the traction
control on this car is really good yeah
we don't even have snow time so we have
like Olson fair ball seasons yeah
turn it off go get another get higher
I'm giving em Airport this house just go
straight
[Music]
people ask me for a wrap
we'll probably write a blog post at the
end of this trip we say the same thing
to a Brazil do the same questions every
school right and ignore a lot of yeah
we're gonna try and compile like a blog
post the question of is my ex car
compatible with open fire
we have the list too
we're on our way to Denver you guys I'm
excited looks like I was here like I was
driving it you can just take it
advantage with people
oh yeah I'm front of them listen
California everyone's so aggressive you
can't even big people a girl in
California we don't get the New York man
no it's way worse I know I think it's
way worse in New York no you don't
understand like so anyway there's so
many worktops in New York so like you
can't really be that again sir that's
true no one's ever gotten there's no
cops in San Francisco San Francisco is
an occurrence I feel like wow
hey joe romeiro another deadly is deadly
you're live what the kilowatt I know
we're live I can express my feelings
about the poor leadership it's a success
can still be just learned and had the
personals dad but the end of every
political career will hopefully give
birth to something new a beautiful
oh there's some of your tools in
Colorado where they charge you like
every few miles that easy enough
everybody like a few cents every mile
we're 60 miles
Wow so the normal you have to say neo
Paradis settings
when you pair it with open palettes salt
if your Neos paired you login did you
login maybe we didn't change the pairing
dialog
Oh instead of Guiana he is still running
loves himself
it's not like we said
yeah I did it just like so
61-59 my love the banshee fabulous idea
oh yeah
people who VP questions should be banned
so that group of people are just being
paste people already have some questions
later
what are you doing this for what is the
need I'd like to actually know
right where's we have pots maybe dance
oh yeah reporter all right Oh someone on
your fork oh nice oh by the police
about it's not illegal you guys wow all
streams get breaks go because they ask
question they are they've repaid
questions that people already asked oh
yeah these like they have og content but
they don't don't freak people
they take people on real people
don't worry we're not talking too fast
we're driving exact specs driving
exactly
I'm sorry
but they can't accelerate this big truck
they're trying to get over the trunk
this doesn't squeeze their way now
we should be
Beverly Hills
it does feel better when you think
there's more people looking at the neon
neon next to each other is incredible
that yeah and the sign is so good
exactly what we want to do look at an
iPhone X compared to like an iPhone 7
you're like wow but really I agree this
is the future right yeah it's scary how
quickly like you look at something new
and the old thing just looks it looks a
bird
I got a new back yourselves the neo
never looked good no but I got a new
MacBook this year just looking at my old
MacBook and if you guys think the eon
looks good well next year no I mean
things only get better right that's how
things work that's technology well some
companies make crappier second wow
that's
oh yeah any other warm
got some more
oh yeah we got we got fly has got flying
JJ dude it's already here though that's
awesome George got a triple XL xxx out
yeah I was going for the double XL
double XL like at Marshall Mathers but
right
still waiting for that exit
we have told you this
what's the O with the medicine is a 128
64 gig it's double iw like space you got
more space you can fit more drives you
can download more songs on Spotify you
can install the exclusive open pilot 128
gig it didn't just impress you just
record for longer without uploading if
you're driving across like Cordoba I
don't even know if Cordoba is a real
place but they mentioned it in Bojack
horseman you should right now you do if
you're installing it now it's zero point
three point nine not zero point four
open pilot won't boot up unless you have
a cinder
well or if it connects to Wi-Fi right
then yeah if you have the tethering
settings yeah try but we didn't like we
were out of service
we're out of service and we're only
because we're only doesn't actually
mobile so we couldn't boot our yawn this
is running a pilot chipper plus can move
without a sin
once we got service my food
and we could engage
when making videos on the end is there
anything virtually Christmas applause in
the settings like Donnelly
like clear out not really that's not
really a secret it's not like someone
can use that information to like access
your drives or anything your dog laddie
is maybe kind of like your license plate
right so if you think blurring out a
license plate is important flare out of
don't let it
but obviously everybody else in the
world can see you
I'm an assembler
there's no secret right Douglas come on
your internal user look at this driving
through this construction
a little bit more than making that
chicane
mr. Canton
just that quick tight shirt
what back in accent yeah we're losing
sir too far to the left
okay this is the thing it's afraid of
the wall it knows to stay away from
walls but like just a really a wide
it was a minimum Lane
the Scottish
remember guys oppai was a level 2 system
pay attention at all times I don't know
maybe I think cuz that truck was over
terrible to him
you can use this on places where you try
them on the right-hand side of just cuz
I don't like the idea there's still left
drivers that's why this damn it
bloppy your governments people
all right it's get again out of the
walls gone yeah there's a furball
what is there there's chick-fil-a here
there's chicken I loved you so they
walked right
chickens is that what is there one right
here
thanks that how far away your wife
suffered I guess not for chicks ouch
yeah yes yeah I mean I guess I did eat a
chicken nuggets
but the a chicken two dollars oh wow
that is Christian commitment right yeah
but it's good marketing like I want it
more now good job Scotland I didn't have
an opinion on Scottish independence
before but now that I've heard that
Danny come
yeah my life City
I really like this is a few Chick Corea
periscope at camera womaning we was into
this song last night called periscope
and we were very disappointed that it
wasn't about you guys oh yeah that's
cool what a kaleidoscope kaleidos goes
law enforcement is on interesting
tired - what all time sometimes our ways
to take exits yeah soon TM now we got a
ship peanuts first after ship peanuts so
honestly probably for that not until the
second half of next year
but yo you all see what we're doing
honestly if it's green and that bar is
going down I can't be doing this right
yeah let's do that bar if I touch the
steering wheel the bar goes back up to
fall right yeah the code is low and if I
press either pedal it disengages so I'm
gonna press the gas right now this is
the age right now obviously it
disengages on the brake and then the bar
will reset as well with speed changes
the bar will reset with sweet changes
good fix that bug yeah and I also wanted
to show your sense be here while you're
changing your speed when yeah if you're
in a different
we call these absolute I think so yeah I
mean there are literally ways and
Spotify right like they're running an
EOS which is just an Android port that's
how we can run Spotify anyways it's just
like it's just like it's an Android
phone yeah it's a modified version of
Android to go remove a lot of the crap
so he can't drive
you know that's fixed we got an Amber
Alert once you're used to get Amber
Alerts
shut it all of that
very deep work out
people are joining us against how many
pots goodbye yeah I'm gonna do out there
or bar but what do they get out of it
like I give those links in Paris compost
like it's not like they're talking about
like hey man you know when does window
0.4 come out alright check out this free
viagra okay I don't think they even let
you post links even without a link they
could still be shilling for something we
don't have that we don't have like go
here go to crypto kitties and buy some
kitties today you know who didn't
Facebook Facebook live because they're
promoting Facebook live they want to get
people on periscope right that's the
only person I could think of who would
have an incentive yeah it's a mess with
periscope or maybe YouTube maybe YouTube
YouTube and Facebook seen it like why
don't we pick periscope just because the
Twitter links to Twitter you really love
Twitter I actually think Twitter is
partially responsible for tearing the
fabric of polite society apart yeah but
I think Twitter knows this to it that's
why they have to a Canadian character so
that you can bring it back together with
another
go for that um see these two the bar
reset when I touch the wheel but no no
no because you can actually express a
much more nuanced than fit into a T then
you can at one forty one forty all you
can do is scream
there's gonna be less to eat
last week how do you measure engagement
from character for dreams
it's not going too well for that you
leave in the car do you take it out
maybe usually leave it
yeah marry ons have security so so it
takes one of our yards we can hot track
them down pretty fast
and good luck turning it off are eons
have security oh we should ship this
attorney stuff to everybody said I'm
like yeah yeah get stolen you can like
you know do like to catch a predator but
for Young's turn on the front facing
camera today
yeah posted posted on Reddit you know
this person yeah so we can trigger the
cameras with all the new stuff not on
you're not holding only on our total
wiry
yeah all our games right yeah
just like all the Tesla's all your
Tesla's are on a VPN just all our eons
are on yet we may eventually put them on
a VPN like Tesla but once it's way more
consumer we wouldn't do that for
something called Afghan
you can pull a you're fast now you
complain about me going slow can't make
it I'm happy 70 miles per hour going
downhill
climbing lane one half of my life you're
into climbing brother
check out this Lane actually you know
what people can't realize people think
like all the pilot like waivers a little
bit there so do keep yeah people hit the
leylines on blogs yeah
my County but so many times you hit the
link yeah yeah it's at four oh yeah but
like Obama still shouldn't waiver being
that should make this all a lot better
see like that was soon as well
well it's more like it's about waiting
you're doing right right and we're able
to sit back and judge it yeah like if
you were to hit the lane I'd call you
out as well no I don't think you would I
really don't think you would I mean I
make a face I don't know yeah there's
rumble strips everyone in the car kind
of good one yeah just a detective
accelerometer I know right we need
microphone it's detect honk miss awesome
honk detector of the factor we got well
we also need an actuator to hump yeah a
guy by the bay like I'm talking about
yeah we don't want to see you in a
level-4 car beside gas brake it's
tearing they're like honking I'll get
our best engineers on yeah the word is I
can actually yeah
the only question is is the button tied
right to the relay or is there some way
to like trying to contribute it was
actually electronic at least on this
contest that will add that to shiver
yeah right where you'd like having honky
music to do anything literally if you
have a panda and a car and Scheffer we
can make ship or honk for you what
exactly does that entail okay so you got
like TomTom here deep map bunch of
companies thinking that they're going to
rent seat and make money by licensing
the map to car manufactures I am going
to figure out what's on HD maps that
people want we're gonna use our massive
data sets and resources to create those
HD Maps and then we're going to give
them away to further our continual war
against rent-seeking
have a damn
see that massive arrival
it's Rocky Mountain National I phone X
looks deadly to the reality that's what
however a Apple's really gonna sell
there a are good goggles yeah yeah I've
seen the IKEA app Ben I do you like set
up your house Mikey's gonna kill it they
have the this furniture happens well you
can virtually place furniture and now
they've bought TaskRabbit oh right so
you're gonna be able to virtually set up
furniture and then click the make it
real button throw you have your blinker
on bro bro so you'll make it real see
we're about to run out of this bar so
we're gonna get a user distracted
I mean if someone's book will always
hire people if they're good so I could
just like tap this they didn't fix the
bog he didn't go away right away I
thought that was fixed
that's the plank and if you're watching
this and he's incredible we should reach
to telescope he's Andy was commas 2017
Employee of the Year
you know doing an incredible job with
chipper with with the UI you see now
growing his team goalies team and now as
a three-person team it's the only real
team okay all the other teams are one
person too
yeah productive you get a team money
image here um because we're not dama
curving alright so what a lot of
pictures do so this is actually what the
world really looks like we don't so a
gamma curve basically accentuates the
middle and drop oh sorry accentuates the
ends and like drops off resolution
around the middle we could have a curve
it we will we well but by 0.5 we're
gonna start we're gonna roll out like
all the HDR features and stuff and also
60fps video these these eons can all do
60fps 1080p HD video they look really
good we might even use neural networks
for adaptive shutter speeds so if you're
going under a bridge you'll know how it
needs to adapt the shutter speed to keep
[Music]
my dream is like for the end of next
year to make videos that just look
unreal like like you described you know
what the iPhone acts is probably doing
this right now yeah cuz they're using
waters Apple has great yeah nobody those
are you saying you're saying it looks
better than reality my gonna make
something looks better than reality
other people and not not plenty in the
next year what we say about open pilot
is like well open pilot in conjunction
with a person that drives better than
people open palette by itself just not
even close to drive as well as a person
I'm a new low for winter but yet the
safety case is you drive you know I'm
sitting here open files doing some stuff
I'm doing some stuff
they're not that much
see adapter shutter speed for that
bridge that's what your needs yeah
a guy acting like a supervisory model on
top of all the powers side you know
and predicting when it will mess up
correct
but you know it saves me CPU suck
all those video features for open
palette as well
oh yeah yeah yeah shaver buzzing all the
pilot are gonna stay pretty much in sync
shaver pluses is okay without the
controls the advantage to shipper plus
is you get a bit more cpu so like ways
it's going to run a bit faster and stuff
my 60 fps
y61
ok so right now we're doing 20 so 60 is
a multiple of 20 and no one's ever heard
of 40 MPs and it's also the max we can
do across the camera bus if we want to
keep so it's actually across the cameras
we'd actually be getting 4 megapixels
back to the sensor which is which is
double technically
but then wewe downscale it doesn't fit
in the background all right
alligator alligator
yeah
I like
we did we put whatever our spot where we
got any song requests please still going
keeping my hands on the wheel when we
pass that instructs Beyonce
I like that
[Music]
a wall
Hey look everything it'll use a little
bit more
not too much
[Music]
the long song yeah I would like the long
one
[Music]
so much more
Oh Oh Louie is okay well it will segment
be running on that you know why you walk
that do it we do good I have the second
I've been running across your videos
right now
[Music]
baby uh committee offer that download I
don't know I used only see the use
school
he's in the nest mm like when asked mm
what else could it make it a little
champagne around that a car kind of uses
be tender you know about beat a like it
that car is a beat and like 5,000 rpms
like the Pistons start going further
digging deeper into the end inter and
you get more power in Tennessee Tech do
they still make us mm now they stop they
like 2004 and 2009 with two years I
think only two years Wow
or maybe all through those years I don't
know the 2009 us left
maybe so for I don't know
yeah they're great I was debating we
Pecola David I've I was debating a
Porsche Boxster that's 2000
there's a cool car thing
you know you know there are you know
it's made the motivation Wow who'd have
thought a four-door sedan is the new
cool car now the Tesla Roadster red but
ya know it's like really really there
aren't any cool cars the car looks the
same
any any song requests in scobie's
Lobo fans Chuck I found it this is the
best way to use your healing yeah don't
cover the camera you feel that
but obviously Rochester
anyone's house but your favorite cars
favorite car
I had a GTI for a while manual GTI
that's pretty sweet
it's one of my favorites no no I just
like hatchbacks a lot
[Music]
and we should recommend that you rubber
duck yeah you'll want to see this
do another time complexity of one
it's a little kid like he's in Russia in
the music video
Russian like Stalin just put some
Russian he's actually huge in Russia
like shout-out to his Russian Gustav it
might work you can also have been doing
Spotify you can obviously do it for your
from play on my yeah that's a driving
well tell them we'll all see him at the
meeting at 10 yep from the car we'll be
driving you like to drive them as though
11 yeah yeah well deserve it well be ten
for us
[Music]
the one I was thinking is that cute Jeep
that's like like a very cute city smart
card with the X lights the X ray does it
have doors yes
Oh week oh you gotta get rid of the
doors totally the cool wall I still
gotta watch Grand Tour bantha such a top
gear fan
watch enough
like you've ever been collared Oh like
you said like a side of the room and
then like we'd like to go she ate we're
like what a good TV on my side couch are
your son there's the GP they would watch
stop here
and then you have
I like GTI but if you're gonna buy a car
the Civic is really nice car my favorite
car is Maybach
was that word me
maybe maybe rolls-royce phantom he
doesn't want to blows for it
another thing about Craig could
potentially get you know yeah
no but like I'm saying like I want a car
that's like light down babe our family
used to have a Mercedes estimates you
know so it's the poor man's poor clothes
but I want a car like that I want a car
is like new bad back allegedly it has
two cameras that read the road and
adjust the suspension by matically can
do incredible things you know I don't
bet they don't they don't the phone
without like a test it's nice but like
it's a luxury clock look I would say the
build quality of Model S is worse than a
build quality of like an Audi a4
we actually we were just going we
actually recorded this video two months
ago actually
come on we're going living in it's like
the Dharma Initiative though we still
have someone set up to ship the eons in
the pan bro-bro the speed under 75 bro
bro you proud that bro gonna swallow
cooking with 57 right no I thought that
was a reckless no
what is this not distracted don't worry
you I don't like the bright side song Oh
bright side sounds like a little peep it
sounds like your feet right doesn't like
will keep all night Lavelle alright
let's see it's bright side and come over
when you're sober
how many we got see the 65 sought out
for us we respect all authorities you
expect the long one back the law guys we
reviewed the Ten Commandments
[Music]
I don't know what STPs but what is is
the prime one just mode the bigger
battery power it's a different body
everybody's telling me life's short for
I wanted not
brain
that a fourth appease the garden
always right there
the Thornton please just passed me in
the right lane
just calling them out is that legal
could check there because we got the
Panda doing the red in the loo
Colorado does have a lot of prisons
really you know bombers in the cupboard
like they they have like this place
bestowing Terrace roarsome making what
you have a big-name Terrace in Colorado
their cars in like 95 Unabomber was a
word with the code but you know because
you is the University and Airlines Bob
and now they like scan all packages for
explosive and yeah dick she's up there
for just one guy but above the shoe done
the guy put his bomb is underwear and
like we knew what that was going but we
drew a line we drew a loner yeah now we
have those devices
no you're on to be honest yeah that's
what we have instead liveability
every time one terrorist comes up with
like some stupid failed plot we now have
to spend another billion dollars that's
a new security
people are outraged about that machine
like I'm saying how it like sometimes if
I Miceli unique if I'm at the airport
early and have time to spare I will opt
out just to be difficult just like other
people are like rushing to make their
flight I'm like yeah you should get that
if you just do you say it's easy
[Laughter]
bomb 3
you have to really interviewed for
gratitude yeah like an hour I'm scared
to go to Israel like they were there
doing the grilling stuff along - yeah I
went like
[Music]
my vision check are we like close
yeah that's right that's why Mathieu you
keep them
my friend actually no that's still a bug
for that but I am gonna watch the bar so
right now it's on rad I'm going to touch
the wheel and now it's back to green
I wish this roof were taller so I could
like really like this is a pretty good
spot
but this pop-up camper we haven't it any
stability hey George you should move
your seat back a little dangerous
only yeah only if it's safe
it wouldn't let you put your seatbacks
toyota that would let you see back
dancing
yo my amazing filming us cause back up
to 52 we were at 36 for a little while
oh by the way we're crushing it right
now 32 that was before me
this is what I live out will beep dream
yeah yeah
if anyone ever goes to what time I mean
last night you got to give a plug for
Homewood speeds
uh-oh the Homewood Suites in our Rock
Springs box for sick man so those senses
for dollars yeah we each got our own bed
all the breakfast this morning about
waffles so you still got a banana
somewhere
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm sure it's a great place it's like
sad like that's what we know it
I got a hand on the wheel off
I'm not touching you we respect all
authority
some people drive with their knees look
as long as you can drive statistically
safely I don't care yeah all right you
can't drive drunk because statistically
you're unsafe yeah can you drive I
really would love to see some large
guest stars clearly not as dangerous to
being drunk
you have slower
[Music]
go go go go three three miles
you
you can get all your logs Cabana your
data is your data and export we don't do
this for like the reason like it's
difficult is really just this we're lazy
we're gonna work on flex would've every
day
same think of your CLE donor how much
your plea donor you want to put a lot of
cars on mud shiver or open violent what
we can do is we give you a back-end
account they can access or believe
just like like say someone like monitor
say upbeat Boulder wanted to buy and
kyon from all their cars and we'd be
happy to get that fielder access to all
those evils right my friend last night
was fun yeah any bless we don't do
business development you have to like
buy all the eons first and then say life
you know what I'm the buyer of all these
eons I want to register to this account
but not gonna like do phone calls with
you click literally until you go in a
store business development
well people will Tracy had a breakup
they were things I never liked they were
like made together boy click man
many people we got leave y'all a little
bit do you guys like want to come to
Arby's with us I probably yeah
Center that I haven't said that much
time in Denver proper really once I
think I stood
yeah it's really nice like there's a
free bus that'll like take you across
the whole stretch in the downtown
not again sandwich shop three bosses
yeah Fairless square in Portland hope
it's still a thing
almost describes it right there take off
that light round
the phallus curve was great I remember
2004 come to Poland or I'm going this
paradise man it's a free rail it's free
it's free that's all please call Perlas
marriage thought was the most incredible
thing like through that before I'm like
14 and like wow I can get her out
[Music]
this car in front of us reminds me
another cool car like is the Fiesta ST
real tiny that afford it supports the in
here is sucks with the turbine but
driving in itself all right
it's got a 1.6 liter and the only
[Music]
oscillate the only acceptable car for
makes an f-150 that's what you're really
good at yeah that's the only also sell a
one liter fiesta that gets like 35 miles
per gallon wait a jump point for though
driving is better it's just that the
experience is so much better
that's for that we did the us we WI yeah
yeah seriously night doesn't happen a
zero point three point nine yeah it's
it's the old you I know waves on Spotify
it just kind of seems like the old one
the driving is the segment
yeah
right into the Sun hands yeah hey I
can't see ladies yeah it's it's hard it
looks like there's this extra strip here
that looks like anxious trips - all
right first real disengage wow that and
the wall good we went like 50 miles
would like to indicate
[Music]
- y'all at the ferris wheel
videos
I love cities I love civilization we've
seen a lot of non cities I mean they
would call themselves
many retired and use retirement speech
you mentioned Budweiser I loved that I
loved that the first thing is I'm going
to go home with a drink and ice cold
blood wise he's saying it the second
time the second time you think I'm gonna
go home I'm gonna drink a nice called
and you're just expected him to say
Budweiser he's like beer
they didn't pay for the shoutout twice I
[Laughter]
don't know I mean that might have even
been like the next level marketing
campaign Budweiser's like the second
time sake beer Budweiser
I mean exactly right everyone's Dignan
like the second time it would have been
totally like damn you sponsored by
Budweiser like by the way guys we're not
sponsored by armies but if any of these
companies would like to sponsor us we
would love to talk but only if you make
it very easy for us like we don't want
much from you if you would just give us
like it camps you could reach out and
give us I can coupon for like a bucket
right like an eight piece chicken bucket
we would like shout out KFC in every
periscope I'm the easiest guy like but
that's the thing I know exactly what
they're gonna do they're gonna reach out
to me with their shitty business
development team we're gonna have phone
calls and they're gonna want to put in
like fifty thousand dollars like bro I
want your fifty thousand dollars all I
love for you is a free bucket of chicken
and I will shout you out in every
periscope literally tens of thousands of
committed people who now want to buy KFC
have you seen how many people watch our
periscope replays yeah drivers to use
over I'll say anything on the Internet
it doesn't matter cuz it doesn't matter
man what are you gonna do you're gonna
regret article about me and make me lose
my job I'm off CEO itch and the Lord I
am the board we do board meetings naked
they go to seven anyways back soon yeah
they can control the erosion peace to
the scopes